CURRICULM VITAE

Abrar Ahmad

S/o Shri Afzaal Ahmad

Contact +91 9639619705 Email-abrarahmad11@yahoo.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

Looking forward to a challenging and competitive work atmosphere, where my skill, talent and abilities will be utilized to the fullest for mutual benefit.

POST APPLIED:

Team Leader A.C. Technician & Electrical Technician

CARRIER SUMMERY:

Work knowledge for the experiences as construction, wire loop checking function from all SG, MCC and Duct testing salability tested, installation power panel, lighting panel, battery bond, ADCC panel, UPS panel all types the panel instrumentation, junction box panel, internal, external wiring and control wiring, cable gelding and termination with control wiring, point to point loop checking, Installation maintenance and repair of split & window A.C etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Total 14 years

- 1) Worked as an senior electrical Foreman in Abdul Aziz Ul Sugair inv.com **Project**: Omran General Hospital 100 beds 22nd March 2009 to 22nd March 2016
- 2) Worked as an AC technician in Blue Star Showroom in India March 2005 to February 2009
- 3) Worked as an AC technician in whirlpool in India April 2002 to March 2005

ACADEMIC EDUCATION:

Higher secondary school

PERSONAL APPRAISAL:

- 1) Be able to work with other people in a team oriented environment as well as work independently to achieve organizational objectives.
- 2) Capable of working effectively for long hours and honor deadlines

PASSPORT DETAILS:	
Passport Number : Date of Issue : Date of Expiry : Place of Issue :	H1790416 25/11/2008 24/11/2018 Bareilly
PERSONAL PROFILE:	
Name : Abrar Ah Father's Name : Shri Afza Date of Birth : 10 th July Marital Status : Married Nationality : Indian Sex Male	al Ahmad
TRAITS:	
Honesty, Hardworking and Det	ermination
LANGUAGE KNOWN:	
English, Hindi & Arabic	
REFERENCE AVAILA	BLE ON REQUEST:
I hereby declare that the detail.	given by me are true to the best of my knowledge belief.
ABOUT SELF:	
to accept challenges as the way	who is self motivated and self driven; I am always ready it comes, which can help me in exploring my potential till of thought, that whatever you do in your life "Its
Date:/	(Abrar Ahmad)